[{"answer": "That aint why, my friend!  It's because you are an alcoholic retard and he had dreams of not eating frozen waffles for dinner every night", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What am I supposed to do with frozen waffles, clamhead?! You put 'em in the toaster and you cook 'em", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend. Are you fucking kidding me", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Heh, we apparently don't say 'side dishes' at the table, either", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well I think you need to spend more time with your friends", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm gonna give Mrs. my friend a call", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Who? my friend? Yeah, yeah, I guess we were", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, because my friend's family doesn't have as much money as we do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Could we go home now, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "But we've been playing for eight hours. We can't think of anything else to do", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Cancer?", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "My ass is collapsing", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes. I'm afraid your ass is collapsing", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes. See this ", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yes. See this ", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, it means that you won't be able to live anymore", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What, bubbeleh, what is it", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oygh. It was for your own good, my friend. I wanted you to get chicken pox while you were young", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well I'm sure you'll find another job soon. Something'll come along", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Now, no", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Wuhwhere's my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend, our son", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend, where are youuu", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend?", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Are you old my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Chicken-pox.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Someone who wants a favor", "qsentId": 28}]